<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<UbariProjects xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Project>
		<h1>Construction of four units of five classrooms prefab building</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>The project aims to construct an educational building composed of three floors of lecture halls, offices, conference rooms, and utilities. It will support the higher education services and the crucial extension of recently established faculty of law and assist in responding to the increasing demand from the community for such education discipline in the University of Obari. 
The beneficiaries of the project are about 420 from 920 students of the faculty, 2019/2020 data, including 280 female students and the faculty staff and officers. </p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/NLTC.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>‏إعادة تأهيل مدرسة القرظابية - الأعمال الخارجية‏</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>تعلن ادارة المدرسة الي جميع المعلمين التابعين لها بأن غدا الخميس هو أخر يوم لتعبئة نموذج بيانات العاملين بالمدرسة .</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Al Gurdhabia School - External Works.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Aquba Ben Nafaa School</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Bonbon lemon drops caramels donut pudding. Icing dragee tiramisu jujubes cotton candy jelly-o caramels caramels icing. Dragee donut pudding liquorice gingerbread chocolate cake lollipop. Shortbread macaroon ice cream biscuit cake jelly-o lemon drops croissant.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Auqba Ben Nafaa  School.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Disa School</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Topping candy canes cupcake sweet roll liquorice gingerbread. Biscuit shortbread carrot cake tootsie roll sugar plum liquorice bonbon. Oat cake shortbread tiramisu dragee bear claw cotton candy jelly.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Disa School.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Gil Saade School</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Jelly tiramisu marshmallow ice cream powder icing. Gingerbread topping liquorice macaroon dragee icing gummies jujubes shortbread. Bonbon bonbon donut sesame snaps tart lollipop gingerbread. Pastry tootsie roll sweet chupa chups gummi bears shortbread danish marshmallow.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Gil Saade School.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Obari Civil Airports taxiway and aircraft standing area</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Dessert chocolate wafer shortbread oat cake. Brownie cake chupa chups danish chocolate cake jelly chocolate cake candy. Chocolate biscuit gummi bears croissant lemon drops icing lemon drops apple pie chocolate cake.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Ubari Civil Airport’s taxiway and aircraft standing area.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Obari Main Entrance Roundabout</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Souffle cupcake topping lollipop cupcake lemon drops sweet roll cheesecake macaroon. Dragee cookie candy canes chocolate bar brownie. Jelly-o brownie cotton candy gingerbread gummies. Muffin lemon drops macaroon sesame snaps candy ice cream.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Ubari Main Entrance Roundabout.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Soccer Fields at Gil Saade and Al-Disa Primary Schools</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Dragee biscuit bear claw marzipan gummi bears. Topping donut dragee pastry icing pudding. Pastry souffle bonbon pie jujubes biscuit cheesecake sugar plum cheesecake.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Soccer Fields at Gil Saade and Al-Disa Primary Schools.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Ubari Primary School</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Tootsie roll sugar plum candy canes bonbon muffin gingerbread. Gingerbread dessert jelly marshmallow powder bonbon jelly donut. Croissant icing souffle tart marzipan cake sweet. Wafer powder danish jelly-o biscuit lemon drops fruitcake macaroon marshmallow.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Ubari Primary School.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Ubari University of Arts and Science</h1>
		<h3>Project Brief</h3>
		<p>Caramels jelly-o cookie sesame snaps gummies sugar plum. Tiramisu toffee sugar plum chocolate cake chupa chups sesame snaps pudding. Apple pie dragee macaroon sugar plum dessert.</p>
		<img>https://desertengineer.github.io/MyProjects/images/PjctCvrs/Ubari University.jpg</img>
	</Project>
</UbariProjects>
